# MaiAda Carpano

Phone: (980) 297 3629 | Email: maiadacx@gmail.com | Philadelphia, PA 19125

GITHUB: http://bit.ly/MaiCGithub PORTFOLIO: http://bit.ly/MaiCPort LINKEDIN: http://bit.ly/MaiCLink

## **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Web Developer with 2 years of professional experience in social media management and web design. Excels at organizing and prioritizing workload demands. Proven to successfully take on leadership roles, collaborate effectively, and build strong relationships with team members. Strong web design and front end development skills with Photoshop, Sass and React.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

**Web Tools:** HTML 5, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, React, Redux, Sass, MySQL, MongoDB, Node.JS, Express, Handlebars, Bootstrap, Github, Devtools, Command Line

UI/UX Design: Responsive Design, Wireframing, Prototyping, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator

#### **PROJECTS**

Pairgy: Website: http://bit.ly/Pairigy | Code: http://bit.ly/PairigyGithub

**Summary:** Pairigy is a social networking site for professionals in and adjacent to tech - such as front end developers, UX designers, and database engineers - to network and interact outside of their own groups.

**My Role**: Project Lead and Full-Stack Developer: I designed the layout and was in charge of designing and building the "Profile" and "Project" features of the site.

**Technologies Used:** Full Stack app built in React, MongoDB Atlas, Node, Express, with JWT authentication and uses Redux to handle state. The UI was designed in Adobe Photoshop and built using Sass and Bootstrap.

BestReads: Website: http://bit.ly/BestReadsWeb | Code: http://bit.ly/BestReadsGithub

**Summary:** BestReads is a Full Stack web application that allows the user to keep track of books that they are currently reading, books they have read in the past and books they hope to read in the future.

**My Role:** Lead Front End Developer: I designed the layout and created the client-side ability to search for books and add books to lists.

**Technologies Used:** The app runs on a Node Express server with Express-Handlebars as its templating engine and Node-Sass as its CSS processor. The MySQL database stores the user's information, which is populated by the GoodReads API. Password.js with Google and Amazon sign in is used for user authentication.

#### RECENT EXPERIENCE

Herdt Consulting // Technical Screener - (2019-Present // Philadelphia, PA)

- Developed new training materials for incoming Purchase Request Creators
- Achieved and maintained a 98% accuracy rate for screening and creating Purchase Requests

Independence Charter School // Teacher - (2018-2019 // Philadelphia, PA)

- Spearheaded a redesign of the K-8 social studies curriculum: Supervised a team of 5 teachers.
- Organized a 2019 National History Day research project event for 7th and 8th graders; Two groups placed at the regional level and continued to the State competition.
- Established a Genders & Sexualities Club; mentored a student-led schoolwide LGBTQ week.
- Earned a performance rating of "Distinguished" (2.7/3.0) on final evaluation.

# **EDUCATION**

Penn LPS - Full Stack Coding Bootcamp - (2019 - 2020 // Philadelphia, PA)

UNC-Charlotte - Graduate Certificate in Teaching - (2010 - 2012 // Charlotte, NC)

John Cabot University - BA in International Affairs - (2005-2009 // Rome, Italy)